<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Accessories &#8211; Quick Money</title>
	<atom:link href="http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney/product-category/accessories/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney</link>
	<description>Shop quick and easy!</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 13:58:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Official Samsung Violet LED View Cover Case &#8211; For Samsung Galaxy S21</title>
		<link>http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney/product/official-samsung-violet-led-view-cover-case-for-samsung-galaxy-s21/</link>
					<comments>http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney/product/official-samsung-violet-led-view-cover-case-for-samsung-galaxy-s21/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[quickmoney]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 13:56:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney/?post_type=product#038;p=146</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<ul>
 	<li>Sleek dot matrix retro notification design</li>
 	<li>Official Samsung accessory made for the Galaxy S21</li>
 	<li>Integrated credit card slot</li>
 	<li>Provides comprehensive protection for your phone and the screen</li>
 	<li>Edge coating with a premium feel</li>
 	<li>Automatic sleep / wake</li>
 	<li>Slimline and durable construction</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h3><img decoding="async" src="https://images.mobilefun.co.uk/graphics/productmisc/83937/Samsung.jpg" alt="samsungbanner" width="725" height="100" /></h3>
<h3>Sleek dot matrix retro notification design</h3>
<p>Beautiful and functional, the Official Samsung LED Cover is also brilliant in terms of form. Featuring a stylish dot matrix design that harks to be a simpler time when dot matrix displays appeared on machines, clocks, railway departure indicators etc. This case will fill you with feelings of nostalgia when you view your notifications in this style.</p>
<p>The LED display details information on your phone&#8217;s status including current time, calls, messages, battery status, volume to name just a few &#8211; viewed quickly and easily from the front of the cover without the need to open the case to view the Galaxy S21&#8217;s screen directly.</p>
<h3>Official Samsung accessory made for the Samsung Galaxy S21</h3>
<p>This is an official Samsung product, so it&#8217;s made to the highest standards with the best quality materials.</p>
<p>It is designed specifically for use with the Samsung Galaxy S21, so offers a perfect fit and does not impede the use of any of the functions including the power and volume buttons, headphone and charging ports or front and rear cameras.</p>
<h3>Integrated credit card slot</h3>
<p>Inside this Galaxy S21 LED cover you&#8217;ll find an intuitively designed slot for storing a card, your ID or even receipts and train tickets while still maintaining its slim design.</p>
<p>This can also be used to store cards that include contactless features, meaning they will never need to be removed from the LED cover.</p>
<h3>Provides comprehensive protection for your phone and the screen</h3>
<p>Protect the front of your Samsung Galaxy S21 from scratches, scrapes and front-on impacts with the official flip cover.</p>
<p>This cover attaches to the back of your device without adding any bulk and then folds over the front when not in use. This means that the most important part of the phone, the screen, is protected from harm with</p>
<h3>Edge coating with a premium feel</h3>
<p>Featuring a special edge coating on the cover provides a premium finish expected with an official Samsung accessory while also benefiting from enhanced grip.</p>
<h3>Automatic sleep / wake</h3>
<p>Samsung have created a premium cover that will wake up your phone&#8217;s display when you open the cover and turn it off again when closed. This preserves your phone&#8217;s battery power, so you can be sure your Galaxy S21 retains its energy when not in use.</p>
<h3>Slimline and durable construction</h3>
<p>Made from high quality synthetic leather materials, this flip cover will keep your Samsung Galaxy S21 screen looking good as new.</p>
<p>The cover is tough enough to withstand day-to-day punishment without blemishing, so both your phone and cover will remain pristine for longer.</p>
<h3></h3>
<div class="product-in-the-box">
<h3>What&#8217;s in the box?</h3>
<ul>
<li>1 x Official Samsung Violet LED View Cover Case</li>
</ul>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney/product/official-samsung-violet-led-view-cover-case-for-samsung-galaxy-s21/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Olixar ArmourDillo Samsung Galaxy S9 Protective Case &#8211; Blue</title>
		<link>http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney/product/olixar-armourdillo-samsung-galaxy-s9-protective-case-blue/</link>
					<comments>http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney/product/olixar-armourdillo-samsung-galaxy-s9-protective-case-blue/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[quickmoney]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 13:53:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney/?post_type=product#038;p=136</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<ul>
 	<li>Two layered case protects from bumps, scrapes and drops</li>
 	<li>Features an impact-resistant polycarbonate exoskeleton</li>
 	<li>Textured grid finishing improves grip and comfort</li>
 	<li>Portable flip-out stand for landscape viewing</li>
 	<li>Cut-outs for the main ports and features of the phone</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img decoding="async" src="https://images.mobilefun.co.uk/graphics/productmisc/88969/Olixar.jpg" alt="fdgsdf" width="725" height="100" /></p>
<h3></h3>
<p><strong>Two layered case protects from bumps, scrapes and drops</strong></p>
<p>This tough protective case has been designed for those with an active lifestyle. It provides great shock and impact absorption thanks to its lightweight TPU polymer with a precisely positioned hard skeleton for added protection. The design of the exoskeleton extends out to protect vulnerable parts of your Samsung Galaxy S9 such as the corners and sides.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://images.mobilefun.co.uk/graphics/productmisc/66093/66093_Misc1.jpg" alt="Olixar ArmourDillo Samsung Galaxy S9 Protective Case - Blue" width="725" height="299" /></p>
<p><strong>Features an impact-resistant polycarbonate exoskeleton</strong></p>
<p>The Olixar ArmourDillo Protective Case features a tough exoskeleton, which covers the back and vulnerable corners of your phone from damage. They are made from an impact-resistant, polycarbonate plastic shell protecting your Samsung Galaxy S9 from accidental damage &#8211; keeping it looking as good as it did when you bought it.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://images.mobilefun.co.uk/graphics/productmisc/66093/66093_Misc4.jpg" alt="Olixar ArmourDillo Samsung Galaxy S9 Protective Case - Blue" width="725" height="299" /></p>
<p><strong>Textured grid finishing improves grip and comfort</strong></p>
<p>Complementing the protective properties of the polycarbonate shell is a textured finish, which not only helps to improve grip when holding the handset, but also makes it more comfortable in the palm of your hand.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://images.mobilefun.co.uk/graphics/productmisc/66093/66093_Misc5.jpg" alt="Olixar ArmourDillo Samsung Galaxy S9 Protective Case - Blue" width="725" height="299" /></p>
<p><strong>Portable flip-out stand for landscape viewing </strong></p>
<p>The Olixar Armourdillo&#8217;s hard attachable exoskeleton doesn&#8217;t just add strength to the silicone shell, but features an ergonomically designed stand that pulls out to give the perfect viewing angle for watching media, web browsing and reading. The stand then simply clicks back into place and lays completely flat so there is zero extra bulk added to the case.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://images.mobilefun.co.uk/graphics/productmisc/66093/66093_Misc6.jpg" alt="Olixar ArmourDillo Samsung Galaxy S9 Protective Case - Blue" width="725" height="299" /></p>
<p><strong>Cut-outs for the main ports and features of the phone</strong></p>
<p>This tough protective case has been designed specifically for the Samsung Galaxy S9 and has cut-outs for the main ports and features of the smartphone such as the camera with flash. The power and volume buttons are covered, but remain functional while encased to give unbeatable protection.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://images.mobilefun.co.uk/graphics/productmisc/66093/66093_Misc3.jpg" alt="Olixar ArmourDillo Samsung Galaxy S9 Protective Case - Blue" width="725" height="335" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney/product/olixar-armourdillo-samsung-galaxy-s9-protective-case-blue/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Olixar Blue Ring Stand Tough Privacy Case &#8211; For Samsung Galaxy A33 5G</title>
		<link>http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney/product/olixar-blue-ring-stand-tough-privacy-case-for-samsung-galaxy-a33-5g/</link>
					<comments>http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney/product/olixar-blue-ring-stand-tough-privacy-case-for-samsung-galaxy-a33-5g/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[quickmoney]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 13:50:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney/?post_type=product#038;p=129</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<ul>
 	<li>Finger loop for extra protection - allows for easy grip of your phone</li>
 	<li>Pull the ring out and have a handy viewing stand to comfortably watch your favourite shows</li>
 	<li>Two-layered case protects from bumps, scrapes and drops</li>
 	<li>Privacy cover slides in front of the camera when not in use</li>
 	<li>Made from a strong, durable lightweight material for long-lasting protection</li>
 	<li>Textured fitting design adds no extra bulk and fits perfectly in your pocket</li>
 	<li>Cut-outs for the main ports and features of the phone; use your device with ease</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img decoding="async" src="https://images.mobilefun.co.uk/graphics/productmisc/88969/Olixar.jpg" alt="fdgsdf" width="725" height="100" /></p>
<h3></h3>
<p>As comfortable as it is stylish, the Olixar blue ring case adds a protective touch to the outside of your phone. With a ring on the back, you have a firm grip on your Samsung Galaxy A33 when you&#8217;re on the internet and sharing content.</p>
<h3>Pull the ring out and have a handy viewing stand to comfortably watch your favourite shows</h3>
<p>This case offers functionality, practicality and protection in one sleek package. Inbuilt into the case is a useful ring feature, which can be pulled out and used as a handy viewing stand to comfortably scroll down social media for hours, watch your favourite movies or provide a clear screen for you to look at whilst you bake. Whatever you want to do that requires you to be handsfree, but still have access to your phone screen; this case will allow you to do that!</p>
<h3>Finger loop for extra protection &#8211; in more ways than one</h3>
<p>This case, not only offers a tough, non-slip design due to the textured finish but also features a useful &#8216;ring&#8217; inbuilt into the case. This ring loop folds flat and out of view if you do not want or need it. But if you do, simply pull the loop out, slip your finger through and you have an extra-secure grip on your phone. This is not only important in the sense that you will not drop your phone under any circumstances, but also in the sense that your Samsung Galaxy A33 cannot be snatched from your hand. So, security against damage and security against theft &#8211; that&#8217;s the beauty of the Olixar ring case.</p>
<h3>Two-layered case protects from bumps, scrapes and drops</h3>
<p>This protective case has been designed for those with an active lifestyle. It provides great shock and impact absorption thanks to its lightweight TPU polymer with a precisely positioned hard skeleton for added protection. The design of the exoskeleton extends out to protect vulnerable parts of your Samsung Galaxy A33 such as the corners and sides.</p>
<h3>Privacy cover slides in front of the camera when not in use</h3>
<p>Unsecured cameras on your Galaxy A33 present the possibility that someone else might be peeping in on your most private moments. None other than the former FBI director James Comey recommended that we all cover our webcams with tape for security reasons. Comey believes that doing so is a simple step for people to &#8220;take responsibility for their own safety and security.&#8221;<br />
Apparently, he doesn&#8217;t want to be spied on and really, who does? In questions during a conference at the Center for Strategic and International Studies, Comey revealed that cam-covering is commonplace at the FBI and other government offices. &#8220;It&#8217;s not crazy that the FBI director cares about personal security as well,&#8221; he added. &#8220;If you go into any government office, we all have our little camera things that sit on top of the screen, they all have a little lid that closes down on them. You do that so people who do not have the authority don&#8217;t look at you.&#8221;</p>
<p>Beat the hackers and stay safe with this Galaxy A33 ring and camera cover case. Quickly gain or deny access to your devices&#8217; camera with this sliding cover. An easy low tech solution to a high tech problem. Once your protective case is on your Galaxy A33, you can slide the cover over your camera to physically deny access to it, then quickly slide it back to gain access to it.</p>
<h3>Textured design adds no extra bulk and fits perfectly in your pocket</h3>
<p>This Olixar ring case from Olixar features a simple, yet stylish design, ensuring your Samsung Galaxy A33 is kept looking stunning whilst being protected. Durable and long-lasting, the case runs neatly around your Samsung Galaxy A33&#8217;s edges to provide excellent side protection as well as a raised lip that guards against damage when placed face down on a flat surface. The back of your new smartphone is also protected against scratches, splashes and any other bumps and scratches. This keeps your Samsung Galaxy A33 looking just as fresh as when you first took it out of the box.</p>
<h3>Cut-outs for the main ports and features of the phone; use your device with ease</h3>
<p>This case has been designed specifically for the Samsung Galaxy A33 and has cut-outs for the main ports and features of the smartphone such as the cameras with flash. The power and volume buttons are covered but remain functional while encased to give unbeatable protection.</p>
<p>Please note: We advise that users of this case ensure that the screen is kept clear of any dust and other small particle debris.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney/product/olixar-blue-ring-stand-tough-privacy-case-for-samsung-galaxy-a33-5g/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Olixar ArmourDillo Samsung Galaxy A5 2017 Tough Case &#8211; Black</title>
		<link>http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney/product/olixar-armourdillo-samsung-galaxy-a5-2017-tough-case-black/</link>
					<comments>http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney/product/olixar-armourdillo-samsung-galaxy-a5-2017-tough-case-black/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[quickmoney]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 13:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney/?post_type=product#038;p=121</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<ul>
 	<li>Two layered case protects from bumps, scrapes and drops</li>
 	<li>Includes an impact-resistant polycarbonate exoskeleton</li>
 	<li>Textured grid finishing improves grip and comfort</li>
 	<li>Cut-outs for the main ports and features of the phone</li>
 	<li>Portable flip-out stand for landscape viewing</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img decoding="async" src="https://images.mobilefun.co.uk/graphics/productmisc/88969/Olixar.jpg" alt="fdgsdf" width="725" height="100" /></p>
<h3></h3>
<p><strong>Two layered case protects from bumps, scrapes and drops</strong></p>
<p>This protective case has been designed for those with an active lifestyle. It provides great shock and impact absorption thanks to its lightweight TPU polymer with a precisely positioned hard skeleton for added protection. The design of the exoskeleton extends out to protect vulnerable parts of your Samsung Galaxy A5 2017 such as the corners and sides.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Features an impact-resistant polycarbonate exoskeleton</strong></p>
<p>The ArmourDillo case features a tough exoskeleton which covers the back and vulnerable corners of your phone from damage. They are made from an impact-resistant, polycarbonate plastic shell which will protect your device from accidental damage &#8211; keeping it looking as good as it did when you bought it.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Textured grid finishing improves grip and comfort</strong></p>
<p>Complementing the protective properties of the polycarbonate shell is a textured finish, which not only helps to improve grip when holding the handset, but also makes it more comfortable in the palm of your hand.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Portable flip-out stand for landscape viewing </strong></p>
<p>The hard attachable exoskeleton doesn&#8217;t just add strength to the silicone shell, but features an ergonomically designed stand that pulls out to give the perfect viewing angle for videos and pictures. The stand then simply clicks back into place and lays completely flat so there is zero bulk added to the case</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Cut-outs for the main ports and features of the phone</strong></p>
<p>This case has been designed specifically for the Samsung Galaxy A5 2017 and has cut-outs for the main ports and features of the smartphone such as the camera with flash. The power and volume buttons are covered, but remain functional while encased to give unbeatable protection.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney/product/olixar-armourdillo-samsung-galaxy-a5-2017-tough-case-black/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Olixar ExoShield Black Tough Bumper Case &#8211; For Samsung Galaxy A23 5G</title>
		<link>http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney/product/olixar-exoshield-black-tough-bumper-case-for-samsung-galaxy-a23-5g/</link>
					<comments>http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney/product/olixar-exoshield-black-tough-bumper-case-for-samsung-galaxy-a23-5g/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[quickmoney]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 13:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney/?post_type=product#038;p=114</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<ul>
 	<li>Made from robust and hard-wearing materials for superior protection</li>
 	<li>Reinforced corners provide excellent protection where it's most needed</li>
 	<li>Non-slip coating for firm grip</li>
 	<li>Slim-fitting design adds slides perfectly in your pocket</li>
 	<li>Raised bezels for camera protection</li>
 	<li>Precise cut-outs so you'll never need to take the case off</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img decoding="async" src="https://images.mobilefun.co.uk/graphics/productmisc/88969/Olixar.jpg" alt="fdgsdf" width="725" height="100" /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Made from robust and hard-wearing materials for superior protection</h3>
<p>Each Olixar ExoShield case for your Samsung Galaxy A23 is made from reinforced bonded Thermo polyurethane and high-quality polycarbonate materials, which makes it flexible enough to absorb impact from drops and bumps, but hard enough to resist potential damage.</p>
<h3>Reinforced corners provide excellent protection where it&#8217;s most needed</h3>
<p>Taking the classic snap-on shell design and adding reinforcement where you need it most, the ExoShield provides better protection than any other case of that type. The vulnerable corners of your phone are the most exposed area should you ever happen to drop it, so the added peace of mind the reinforced corners provide is priceless &#8211; especially for the slight increase in size. Not only do the corner bumpers extend outwards across the length and width of your phone, but they also extend out across the depth of your phone. This is important because it adds screen protection by keeping it off from any flat surface. It also protects the raised rear camera too in much the same way.</p>
<h3>Non-slip coating for firm grip</h3>
<p>The selected materials used have a non-slip coating that provides you with extra grip for your phone, which minimises the chance of dropping your device &#8211; meaning this case is professional enough for work and sporty enough for play. And after all, the best defence against drop damage is not dropping your phone in the first place.</p>
<h3>Slim-fitting design adds slides perfectly in your pocket</h3>
<p>The Olixar ExoShield case is designed to be slim, lightweight and strong &#8211; so you can be assured that this case will add virtually no extra bulk to your Samsung Galaxy A23 and will still fit in your pocket with ease.</p>
<h3>Raised bezels for camera protection</h3>
<p>This case has a raised bezel that prevents your Samsung Galaxy A23&#8217;s screen from coming into contact with any flat surface when you place the phone face down. This prevents your Samsung Galaxy A23 screen from getting any unwanted scratches and dirt on it. In terms of camera protection, the ExoShield also excels here with the bezel extending beyond the rear of the case and being easily the first point of contact with any impact, rather than your precious camera lens. Keep snapping without any horrible scuffing and scratching getting in the way.</p>
<h3>Precise cut-outs so you&#8217;ll never need to take the case off</h3>
<p>Each Olixar ExoShield has been designed specifically for the Samsung Galaxy A23 and features cut-outs for the various ports and features &#8211; such as the rear-facing camera and charging port. There are also button covers to protect the phone&#8217;s vulnerable controls.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney/product/olixar-exoshield-black-tough-bumper-case-for-samsung-galaxy-a23-5g/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Promate 3-in-1 Charging Kit With USB-C Cable, Car Charger &#038; EU Plug</title>
		<link>http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney/product/promate-3-in-1-charging-kit-with-usb-c-cable-car-charger-eu-plug/</link>
					<comments>http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney/product/promate-3-in-1-charging-kit-with-usb-c-cable-car-charger-eu-plug/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[quickmoney]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 13:35:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney/?post_type=product#038;p=106</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<ul>
 	<li>Ultimate Fast Charging Kit with EU Plug</li>
 	<li>Compact design</li>
 	<li>Qualcomm Quick Charger 3.0</li>
 	<li>Adaptive fast charging wall charger</li>
 	<li>Safety Guaranteed</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h3>Ultimate Fast Charging Kit</h3>
<p>Thus ultra-fast charging kit from Promate is everything you will need to keep your device ready and charged wherever you are! The kit contains the high-power wall charger and a car charger, which will charge your USB compatible device up to 75% faster. Just plug in the high-quality type- C cable allows you to connect your device to charge or to sync the data simultaneously.</p>
<h3>Safety Guaranteed</h3>
<p>No need to worry about the safety of your charging devices. The Promate UniGear USB Mains Charger features over-charging, overheating and over-current protection to completely minimize the chances of your devices being damaged.</p>
<h3>Specifications</h3>
<p>Input: 12-24V (Car Charger), 100-240V (Home Charger)</p>
<p>Output:3.6-5V/3A, 5V-9V/2A, 9V-12V/1.5A (Car/Home Charger)</p>
<p>Input Interface: Car Lighter Adapter, Standard Plug</p>
<p>Output Interface:1 QC 3.0 USB Port (Car/Home Charger)</p>
<p>Cable Lenght: 120 cm</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney/product/promate-3-in-1-charging-kit-with-usb-c-cable-car-charger-eu-plug/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Olixar iPhone 13 mini 18W Mains Charger &#038; USB-C to Lightning Cable</title>
		<link>http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney/product/olixar-iphone-13-mini-18w-mains-charger-usb-c-to-lightning-cable/</link>
					<comments>http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney/product/olixar-iphone-13-mini-18w-mains-charger-usb-c-to-lightning-cable/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[quickmoney]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 13:31:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney/?post_type=product#038;p=98</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<ul>
 	<li>70% faster than 5W charging</li>
 	<li>Charge and sync</li>
 	<li>Designed specifically for 18W power</li>
 	<li>Adapts to device</li>
 	<li>Contains Olixar Black 18W Braided Lightning to USB-C Charging Cable</li>
 	<li>Contains Power Delivery Black 18W Single USB-C Wall Charger</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of the most irritating things is when you want to go out, but your phone battery is too low. Luckily, with the 18W fast mains charger and lightning to USB-C charging cable, you can charge your iPhone 13 mini 70% faster &#8211; allowing you to get out with your friends faster, secure in the knowledge that your phone will have charge for your next adventure.</p>
<h3>70% faster than 5W charging</h3>
<p>As technology develops, chargers do too. If combining the 18W mains charger with the USB-C to Lightning Cable, your iPhone 13 mini can charge up to 70% faster &#8211; meaning you don&#8217;t need to keep your phone on charge overnight and damage the battery. Instead, you can plug it in when needed, get on with something else, and take it out less than 2 hours later. This time extra power means less responsibility &#8211; what more could you want?</p>
<h3>Charge and sync</h3>
<p>Depending on what laptop you have, you can insert your Black Olixar USB-C to Lightning Charging Cable into your laptop, as well as the PD 18W Wall Charger. Charge your iPhone 13 mini and sync it to apple, allowing your phone to back up, keeping your photos and device content safe.  This also gives some versatility as if you have forgotten your Olixar 18W Fast Mains Charger, you can still charge your device effectively.</p>
<h3>Designed specifically for 18W power</h3>
<p>Both the 18W fast mains charger and USB-C to Lightning cable are specifically designed to carry this increased wattage without being damaged or overheating, for enhanced safety to users and their devices.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter" src="https://images.mobilefun.co.uk/graphics/450pixelp/86837.jpg" alt="imahe" width="450" height="450" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney/product/olixar-iphone-13-mini-18w-mains-charger-usb-c-to-lightning-cable/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Goui Black Waterproof 1.5m USB-C Lightning Cable</title>
		<link>http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney/product/goui-black-waterproof-1-5m-usb-c-lightning-cable/</link>
					<comments>http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney/product/goui-black-waterproof-1-5m-usb-c-lightning-cable/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[quickmoney]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 13:27:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney/?post_type=product#038;p=94</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<ul>
 	<li>Waterproof design</li>
 	<li>1.5m length</li>
 	<li>Allows Simultaneous Charging And Syncing Of Your Lightning Device</li>
 	<li>Superfast USB-C charging</li>
 	<li>Connect to any Apple USB-C lightning-supported devices</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h3><img decoding="async" src="https://images.mobilefun.co.uk/graphics/productmisc/93509/3.jpg" alt="n" width="512" height="71" /></h3>
<h3>Waterproof design</h3>
<p>Never worry about annoying spillages again as this Goui Black Lightning Cable is completely waterproof and dust-proof! It also comes with caps at the ends for added protection.</p>
<h3>1.5m length</h3>
<p>Imagine what you can do with a 1.5m durable cable that you couldn&#8217;t before? You can toss and turn in bed, whilst keeping your device on charge. Or, if you&#8217;re at a hotel and they don&#8217;t have plugs near your bed (one of the biggest annoyances of hotels), this lead may be able to reach your bed, allowing you to charge your phone comfortably.</p>
<h3>Allows Simultaneous Charging And Syncing Of Your Lightning Device</h3>
<p>This Official Apple cable allows you to connect your phone to your laptop or computer in order to charge your phone and exchange/sync data simultaneously.</p>
<h3>Superfast USB-C charging</h3>
<p>With the Official Apple USB-C mains charger, you can charge your device faster than ever before with the addition of this high-quality Official Apple Lightning to USB-C Cable.</p>
<h3>Connect to any Apple USB-C lightning-supported devices</h3>
<p>Designed to connect Lightning phones and tablets including iPhone, iPad, iPad Air, iPad Mini, and iPad Pro (all iPad models from 2021-2022) devices to a USB charger or USB Port for charging and synchronizing.</p>
<p><em><strong>Please note: This product comes in bulk packaging</strong></em></p>
<h3>Compatibility:</h3>
<p>iPhone 5</p>
<p>iPhone 5c</p>
<p>iPhone 5s</p>
<p>iPhone 6</p>
<p>iPhone 6 Plus</p>
<p>iPhone 6s</p>
<p>iPhone 6S Plus</p>
<p>iPhone SE (1st generation)</p>
<p>iPhone 7</p>
<p>iPhone 7 Plus</p>
<p>iPhone 8</p>
<p>iPhone 8 Plus</p>
<p>iPhone X</p>
<p>iPhone XR</p>
<p>iPhone XS</p>
<p>iPhone XS Max</p>
<p>iPhone 11</p>
<p>iPhone 11 Pro</p>
<p>iPhone 11 Pro Max</p>
<p>iPhone SE (2nd generation)</p>
<p>iPhone 12</p>
<p>iPhone 12 mini</p>
<p>iPhone 12 Pro</p>
<p>iPhone 12 Pro Max</p>
<p>iPhone 13</p>
<p>iPhone 13 mini</p>
<p>iPhone 13 Pro</p>
<p>iPhone 13 Pro Max</p>
<p>iPhone SE (3rd generation)</p>
<p>iPhone 14</p>
<p>iPhone 14 Plus</p>
<p>iPhone 14 Pro</p>
<p>iPhone 14 Pro Max</p>
<p>iPad Pro 12.9-inch (2nd generation)</p>
<p>iPad Pro 10.5-inch</p>
<p>iPad (5th generation)</p>
<p>iPad Pro 9.7-inch</p>
<p>iPad Pro 12.9-inch (1st generation)</p>
<p>iPad Air 2</p>
<p>iPad mini 4</p>
<p>iPad mini 3</p>
<p>iPad Air</p>
<p>iPad mini 2</p>
<p>iPad mini</p>
<p>iPad (4th generation)</p>
<p>iPod touch (6th generation)</p>
<p>iPod touch (5th generation)</p>
<div class="product-in-the-box">
<h3>What&#8217;s in the box?</h3>
<ul>
<li>1 x Goui Black Waterproof 1.5m USB-C Lightning Cable</li>
</ul>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney/product/goui-black-waterproof-1-5m-usb-c-lightning-cable/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Official Samsung 25W EU Fast Charger &#8211; Black</title>
		<link>http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney/product/official-samsung-25w-eu-fast-charger-black/</link>
					<comments>http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney/product/official-samsung-25w-eu-fast-charger-black/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[quickmoney]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 13:25:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney/?post_type=product#038;p=86</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<ul>
 	<li>Genuine Samsung product</li>
 	<li>EU wall charger</li>
 	<li>Charge &#38; sync data</li>
 	<li>Compact design allows you to take it on your travels</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img decoding="async" src="https://images.mobilefun.co.uk/graphics/banners/Samsung.jpg" alt="Official Samsung Galaxy S6 / S6 Edge / Note 4 Adaptive EU Fast Charger " width="725" height="100" /></p>
<p>Charge your Samsung device safely, effectively &amp; quickly with this sleek, white Official Samsung 25W USB-C Mains Wall Charger. Not only does this charger quickly power the fastest charging devices, but it’ll also play well with other models too. So for standard PD 3.0 compatible devices you&#8217;ll get a max 25W charge, while others charge at speeds they can handle.</p>
<h3><strong>Genuine Samsung product</strong></h3>
<p>The internet is flooded with cheap fake Samsung chargers and cables that could damage your phone and possibly even cause injury to yourself and your family. At Mobile Fun, we pride ourselves on only sourcing products from respected suppliers that have been authorised by Samsung. So, you can be sure of a top quality accessory that has been manufactured to Samsung&#8217;s recognised quality assurance for the best compatibility and most important of all &#8211; the best safety standards.</p>
<h3>EU wall charger</h3>
<p>This Official Samsung EU Mains Charger and cable allows for Power Delivery. Designed with the latest technology, this charger allows ultra fast charging ensuring your up to full charge in no time. In addition, it is fitted with power surge which prevents your battery being damaged from over-charging as when the device is fully charged, the cable cuts off the power supply ensuring your device is safe. Moreover, this cable allows you to control the flow of charge, meaning you can alter the direction of where the charge goes to and from charging your desired device with ease.</p>
<h3><strong>Adaptive fast charging</strong></h3>
<p>Fast charging uses battery charging technology that charges your Samsung devices battery faster by increasing the charging power however without damaging your battery. These phones support Samsung’s Adaptive fast charging feature and qualcomm technology. This charger is the exact same model that came with your phone, so makes an ideal spare or replacement.</p>
<h3><strong>Compact design allows you to take it on your travels</strong></h3>
<p>The genuine Samsung Galaxy mains charger is small for easy storage and lightweight for carrying around with you for quick and convenient charging. It&#8217;s also extremely portable, making it ideal for taking with you on holidays or short trips.</p>
<div class="product-in-the-box">
<h3>What&#8217;s in the box?</h3>
<ul>
<li>25W EU Mains Charger</li>
</ul>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney/product/official-samsung-25w-eu-fast-charger-black/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Belkin White Bluetooth Speaker and 10W Wireless Charging Stand</title>
		<link>http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney/product/belkin-white-bluetooth-speaker-and-10w-wireless-charging-stand/</link>
					<comments>http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney/product/belkin-white-bluetooth-speaker-and-10w-wireless-charging-stand/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[quickmoney]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 12:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney/?post_type=product#038;p=69</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<ul>
 	<li>One-push Bluetooth pairing, connecting or disconnecting</li>
 	<li>10W fast wireless charging</li>
 	<li>Crystal-clear speaker and microphone</li>
 	<li>Wirelessly charge in portrait or landscape</li>
 	<li>Case-compatible</li>
 	<li>Compact, sleek design</li>
</ul>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h3>Quick Charge, Great Sound</h3>
<p>The SOUNDFORM Charge Bluetooth Speaker + 10W Wireless Charger is the perfect companion for your desk, nightstand, kitchen counter—or anywhere you want to charge and listen. It’s simple to get going with one-push Bluetooth pairing while the streamlined and compact design easily fits anywhere. This case-compatible fast wireless charging stand delivers optimal power for any Qi-Certified device, up to 10W of charge in landscape or portrait orientation.</p>
<h3>10W Qi-Enabled Wireless Charging</h3>
<p>The Belkin SOUNDFORM Charge delivers up to 10W of fast wireless charging for your Samsung, Apple, Google, and other Qi-enabled smartphones and devices in both portrait and landscape orientation.</p>
<h3>Portrait or Landscape Charging</h3>
<p>With the Belkin Bluetooth Speaker And 10W Wireless Charging Stand you can Watch, stream, or video call while your device charges in either direction using the built-in stand on our SOUNDFORM Charge &#8211; charge and listen at the same time!</p>
<h3>Easy, One-Push Pairing</h3>
<p>Connecting your smartphone (android or iPhone) has never been easier, with the Belkin Bluetooth Speaker And 10W Wireless Charging Stand you can seamlessly pair the Speaker + Wireless Charger to any Bluetooth-enabled device with the simple push of a button.</p>
<h3>Designed for Any Environment</h3>
<p>A sleek, compact design complements any home, university accommodation, kitchen counter, or nightstand setup.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://quickmoneystorebusiness.github.io/quickmoney/product/belkin-white-bluetooth-speaker-and-10w-wireless-charging-stand/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
